MOHD AFIFUDDIN BIN MANSOR NO 279. FELDA CHINI 1, 26690 PEKAN, PAHANG DARUL MAKMUR. TEL-0148463703 fudinmansor@gmail.com





SUMMARY

A fresh graduate with a degree in textile technology and work experience in textile testing. A highly motivated, work well under stress, interpersonal, time management and problem solving skills. Able to work independently as well as in group environment and equipped with the hands-on experience of using textile machine.



EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

2013 - Exco for Family Day in Textile Society

Vice of Badminton Competition.

Exco for De Elegant of Paradise Night (Dinner for Textile Society).

Participant, Camping in Expedition Club, Port Dickson.

2014 - Participant, Sukan Antara Fakulti (SAF), Faculty of Applied Science in "Badminton", UiTM.

2015 - Participant, Sukan Antara Kolej

(SUKOL), Perindu in Badminton, UiTM



SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- Computer skills in Microsoft Office Tools
- Working knowledge of Microsoft Words, Power Point and Excel
- Knowledge of Weave Point Software



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCES (HONS.) TEXTILE TECHNOLOGY

Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM) — 2014-2016

GPA 3.30 / CGPA 3.23

DIPLOMA IN TEXTILE TECHNOLOGY

Universiti Teknologi Mara (UiTM) — 2011-2014

GPA 3.34 / CGPA 3.28



WORKING EXPERIENCES

INTERNSHIP

2013-2014

Internship in Science and Technology Research Institute for Defence (STRIDE) for three months starting from 3 December 2013 until 28 February 2014. In this company some research and testing have been done not for textile only. It is including physical testing and material testing.



LANGUAGES

Proficiency to spoken and written in Bahasa Malaysia and good in English and have learn basic of German.



REFERENCE

ASSOC. PROF. DR MOHD ROZI BIN AHMAD

SENIOR LECTURER IN FACULTY OF APPLIED SCIENCE

TEL- 019-3815510 / 03-55443560